Let's kill him too, partner.
If we burn everything,
we'll be the prime suspects.
We need a witness
to speak in our favor.
You're right.
But what if he too speaks
only the truth like his father?
Let's find out right away.
Boy, what's your name?
- Bhavani
- Huh?
Bhavani.
How did your parents die?
They were burnt to death
in a gas cylinder explosion.
He sure knows to survive.
After using him as a witness,
let's file a fake complaint saying
he stole our union funds.
His father was a Lorry Union leader.
Nobody would believe
that he stole union funds.
So compassionate all of a sudden?
He's so young, that's why.
Boy, listen.
I'll send you to a place where they will
take good care of boys like you.
Will you go there?
GOVT. JUVENILE OBSERVATION HOME
NAGERCOIL, KALLAKURICHI
That boy shouldn't sleep
peacefully even for a night.
There's more than
what you asked for.
Thank you, sir.
If there's any foul play,
Esakki will kill you both.
- Better keep an eye.
- I will, sir.
Hey, come here.
What are you glaring at him for?
Get up! How dare you sleep!
What are you looking at?
Clean.
Wipe my boots!
I'll flay you, rascal!
Move aside, everybody.
I've been beating you up
like an animal,
but you don't seem
to be affected at all.
You are hitting me mercilessly
because someone is paying you.
I have to pay you more
to make you stop hitting me.
I am penniless.
Hit me as long as you want.
When I have the money,
I'll call you up.
- Who is this?
- Sir...
Bhavani has escaped from jail.
Is this why
I'm spending so lavishly?
I'll deal with you in person.
Find him before daybreak.
Scumbag!
Don't be scared, sir.
I won't harm you.
I could have slit your throat
while you were asleep, you know.
But I can't be on the run
throughout my life.
I came here to request you
to let me lead a normal life.
I'm not following.
Let me live, sir.
What do I gain by releasing you, huh?
Let me out for a week, sir.
I'll give you half of
what I earn in this time.
If I miss a week,
stab me to death.
Fine, I'll take a chance on you.
This week is yours, go.
How much do you usually pay for a lorry
to cross the check post without a permit?
You've to cough up Rs 1000 per lorry
to be allowed to pass.
I'll get the permit slip.
Rs 1000 is yours to keep.
I just want Rs 100 per lorry.
What if the police interferes?
That's my responsibility.
What is it? What do you want?
'2002-2003 Register'
Go, go, go.
Move, move.
Come, quick
Hey! Wait, wait.
Hurry up.
If you want the permit slip in your hand,
I must get Rs 500 per lorry.
Got it?
Whether I'm here or not,
ensure the boys get
their share of booze and fag.
GOVT. REFORMATORY
In a way, we are
responsible for all this, partner.
When we killed his father,
we should have burnt him to ashes too
Now he's running for the president
of the Lorry Drivers' Union.
How did he amass
so much wealth, sir?
Logu, do you know how many
lorries are under his control?
He also owns a meat factory.
He is into exports too.
But this isn't news, partner.
You know this reformatory
for juvenile delinquents?
He uses those boys to do something.
That's where the money flows in.
Some even say he plays proxy
to the minister to launder money.
If he wins this year's Union Election,
he will definitely avenge
his father's death.
We must act now, partner.
There he is.
Finish him.
You've got Gods of Hindu,
Muslim, Christian
dangling around your neck, why?
I pray to all Gods, you see.
At least, one will save me
when I'm in danger.
Minimum guarantee.
Philosophy?
Is he the same chap who pleaded
for his life at the age of 17?
We need to discuss something
very important with you.
You've been paying us
on a weekly basis all these years, right?
You can stop that.
Instead sell all your assets
and earn a living
somewhere outside this town.
I wanted to talk about this
next week.
How long can I keep paying you
money every week?
I've decided not to pay.
Hey. That decision isn't yours to take,
scumbag!
Just shut up and obey our orders.
I do what I feel is right.
Well...
I'm aware how dirty your hands are.
Making those boys surrender
for the crimes you commit.
Instigating them to kill.
We know all about your business.
Don't show off your temerity.
Just tuck your tail and scoot.
Otherwise, we will kill you.
Look around. This is my area.
I can get you killed right now.
I think you are unable to differentiate
working for money and for loyalty?
Shall I demonstrate?
Listen! We have an important
work to do, come here.
He is calling us, come.
- Bhavani.
- Why is he calling us suddenly?
Whoever kills these three men
right here will be rewarded
with a prize money
of 20 lakh rupees.
Do you realize where you are
and what you are blabbering?
Do you think I'm with him
for money?
We go back a long way.
- 30 lakh rupees.
- It doesn't matter!
- He's like my brother.
- 40 lakh rupees.
Sir, why are you letting him talk?
Just say yes, I'll kill him--
50 lakh rupees.
- How dare you rattle off?
- 60 lakh rupees.
Hey! Kill him!
Wait, sir, let's hear him out.
70 lakh rupees.
- Hey--
- It's all right, sir.
Sir, I'll go watch the gate
and make sure no one enters.
- 80 lakh rupees.
- What!
Move aside.
Then shall we lock
the deal for 80 lakh rupees?
- Okay, sir.
- Are you ready?
We will divide 80 lakh equally.
I'll deal with these three men.
Now do you know the difference
between greed and gratitude?
Sir.
I don't need this.
I'll give you two minutes.
Kill me if you can
and save your lives.
Hey!
These boys?
Yes, sir.
Post mortem matches the crime scene?
They have done a neat job, sir.
Not knowing to drive
they ran over a man.
You expect me to buy this?
Whom are you trying to trick?
Sir, I'm not a professional driver.
I was just trying to drive
and there was an accident.
- Right?
- Yes, sir.
- Do they have a past history?
Pickpocket case, 511.
Then they were in a govt. reformatory
for six months.
Now they are facing
charges under IPC 302.
Is this a reformatory?
Or a criminal training centre?
Why do you need this reformatory
that turns a thief into a murderer?
- Call the Observation home staff.
- Okay, sir.
Sir, he wants to see you.
Greetings, sir.
I am the superintendent here.
Forget the introduction, when do you
intend on employing a regular master?
The boys drive away
any master we appoint.
Actually scared of them,
no teacher wants to take up this post.
But how can you run a school?
Not one teacher so far, huh?
Shocking and shameful!
If there's no master to teach
or guide the students,
how will they reform, huh?
I have personally seen
about 40 cases like this here.
Superintendent, I'm passing a govt. order.
Send it to all private, govt. schools
and colleges, to every single institution
in Tamil Nadu.
You'll find a master
for sure, understand?
Type out the order.
They call me master
Changes will happen faster
MASTER
His entry spells power
Who is our master?
Commander
St Jeffery College is a truly renowned
educational institution in Chennai.
Alumni of this college
have carved a name
in cinema, politics, advertising and
are celebrities in their own right.
This college has molded innumerable VIPs.
Students are very eager to make this
a very memorable reunion.
Do you want to know why?
Come along with me.
- Hi. Ramya.
- Yes.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Same here.
I spoke to you over the phone.
- Oh! That was you?
- Yeah.
Okay, okay.
- What's your full name?
- Charulatha Prasad.
- Nice. I'll introduce you to everyone.
- Sure.
- This college has a decorum.
- Students are capable of doing it.
Their plan is to ruin our image when
the minister arrives as our chief guest.
If this issue leaks,
your college reputation will be at stake.
Take a seat.
If you want to take further action
- do so after the minister leaves.
- This is well planned.
Sri, stop this cat and mouse game.
- You better confess the truth.
- Trust me, sir.
- Isn't JD responsible?
- No, sir.
I swear, no, sir.
Then who is the culprit?
Your father?
Everyone knows about Savitha's trauma.
I know how those two scumbags
sexually harassed her--
Hey! Mind your words.
Spit that gum out first.
I said throw it out.
I'll trash it as soon as
it loses its sweetness.
Don't act smart.
The two noble souls
who sexually harassed her,
were suspended by you for one week.
Knowing it was inadequate,
we even complained to the police.
But they took us for a ride
without taking any action.
Only then did we come know
that Aadith's dad is a rich businessman.
I think he has planned
to send them off to Canada.
That's why I took the boys
to his house
to find out his plan.
Hello, sir, they haven't
left the house yet.
I think they are still inside.
But it's evident they have
hatched a plot to escape.
Strangers are walking
in and out of their house.
Sir, I can hear their voices.
I think they are coming out.
- Take care, Son.
- Don't worry, Dad.
- Be safe.
- I'll call as soon as I reach.
This is the duo.
Call after you reach the airport.
Go, go, go.
Let's follow them.
Both of them have left home, sir.
Aadith and Rahul are in a taxi.
They just crossed Ashok Nagar.
Along with our boys,
I am following them, sir.
- Where are you, sir?
- At a signal.
- Which signal?
- Jafferkhanpet.
Ask him the bus number.
- Which bus?
- 70 V.
Bus number, sir?
70 V.
It's getting closer.
Waiting at the signal now.
Over here.
I've spotted you.
Come on, hurry up.
Look, that's the bus.
Quick!
- Get in.
- Move.
Both of them got into
bus number 70 V, sir.
Bus number TN 01 AN 1184.
The bus just crossed
Jafferkhanpet signal--
Why did he cut my call?
Got the man with the plan right here
Bringin' swag with the man right here
Livin' up and sippin' on beer
Yeah, clap for me, man, right here
Got the man with the plan right here
Bringin' swag with the man right here
Livin' up and sippin' on beer
Yeah, clap for me, man, right here
Hey! No matter what they say
Master the blaster
Hey! No matter what they do
Mister Master the Blaster
Riddim
Hey! No matter what they say
Master the blaster
Yeah! Master the blaster
Hey! No matter what they do
Mister Master the Blaster
Got the man with the plan right here
Bringin' swag with the man right here
Repeat!
Livin' up and sippin on beer
Yeah, clap for me man, right here
Got the man with the plan right here
Bringin' swag with the man right here
Repeat!
Livin' up and sippin on beer
Yeah, clap for me, man, right here
Sound the alarm
Yeah! Give it up for my man JD
settin' fire to the screen
No problem at all.
I've informed our boys.
They are inside the airport.
Don't worry at all.
All loopholes covered.
His entry spells power
Who is our brother?
Commander
Come, let's go.
Not you.
Come.
Hey!
Throw him out.
Who is that?
Professor.
Brother, get up. Come, come.
Hurry up.
Hey driver, don't stop the bus.
Go, go. Keep going.
Don't stop, keep moving.
Stop, stop.
Stop, man.
Let's get off.
Come soon.
They got down from the bus and ran.
Thank God he came in his bike.
- It wasn't him.
- Sorry, sir, he came.
Sir, come.
In all this confusion,
they ran into the Metro station.
Give me the token.
Come fast.
Get in, quick.
CENTRAL METRO
AIRPORT
It's really good.
I never got a chance to take a Metro train
from when it started operating.
Thanks, Boys.
Hey.
I plan to stab a master here.
Brave hearts, continue the ride.
Fainthearted, alight.
Girls, girls.
I'll collect it later.
If you move a bit,
I can go there and watch.
Thanks, sir.
What?
How are college students and
'dhoti' clad politicians connected?
Airport is close by.
Catch an auto or something and go.
Don't wait here.
Hurry up.
They rushed out
and got into a share-auto.
Turned out to be our friend
Jameel's auto, I got in too.
Easy-peasy. That's where they got caught.
- Escape to Canada, right?
- Yes, sir.
Friends encircled and took them
to the police station, right?
Yes, sir.
So you were responsible
for everything.
- Yes, sir.
- JD had nothing to do with this?
- We swear, nothing at all, sir.
Sir.
Those two boys swear
your teacher JD was behind this.
- They are lying.
- Of course, I know, sir.
JD is the culprit.
- Who is JD?
- He is playing up with their support.
- I'll tell you later.
- One day he'll get caught.
That will be his doomsday.
Minister has arrived.
If you are ready, we can
escort him to the auditorium.
Come, come.
Sir, you please sit.
- I'll be back in ten minutes.
- I'll wait.
- Serve him tea.
- Carry on.
Sir, I'll be back in two minutes.
Not picking your call, huh?
It's ringing but he isn't picking.
He's still doing
what he did during his student days!
Shut up! Vanathi, didn't you try?
I spoke with the students.
- What did they say?
- He has been suspended.
If you had told us earlier, we could
have gone in person and brought him.
He must be very busy, try again.
We relish the 'rajma'--
[mobile ringing]
Livin' up and sippin on beer
Yeah, clap for me, man, right here
Uncle, he's our Principal
Anbiah Samuel.
Welcome, sir.
This is our Vice Principal.
Ramya?
If that student is such a troublemaker,
why not just dismiss him?
In that case, he should have
gotten dismissed 20 years ago.
I don't get it.
JD isn't a student, my dear.
Professor!
- What?
- Dean of student affairs.
First of all, we welcome you all.
Good morning to one and all present here.
Our honorable chief guest
Manavai R Gauthaman.
Respected dignitaries on the dais.
What happened?
Sir, students are refusing
to come out from back stage.
Hey!
Did you say you said this function
wouldn't go on without JD?
Then what, sir? We kept
telling you he is innocent.
But you suspended him
for two weeks.
Any other day it's fine, sir.
This alumni meet is only for him.
How can he not be here, sir?
Nothing will happen without him.
So you are the human rights activist?
I'll deal with you later!
Sir, the minister has been
waiting for a long time.
- Please bear with us.
- He cancelled so many appointments.
- Start the program.
- I'll talk to them and join you.
Om Shanti! Om Shanti!
- Call JD.
- You suspended him.
- You call him.
- I don't know his number.
Call him, dude.
Call before he changes his mind.
Hello. JD.
This is Principal Samuel.
JD sir is fast asleep.
Call later.
Principal Anbiah Samuel!
Anbu, forget waking him up.
It's not going to happen.
- He's guzzled down about four bottles.-Will you wake him up or not?
No way!
Hey!
He's drunk.
What can I do?
Will you ask the Education Minister
to wait for half an hour?
We'll go and get him.
- What?
- Do it.
- What happened?
- It's not working.
Is this how you drum-roll?
Getting paid right?
Bump it, fellows.
Rock and roll, man!
This is it. This is what we want.
Ready! Come on!
Master is coming, move aside
Hey, stop!
- Lift him.
- Lift him up!
Speed up!
- Sir, good morning.
- Good morning.
Tea, sir.
The moment our brother steps in
It's like an atom bomb exploding
- Did they really invite me?
- Sir, why this doubt?
I swear they asked you to come.
Brother, beat the drum.
Master coming!
Move aside!
Rock and roll!
Deliberately if you make trouble
It will boomerang on you centuple
If you jeer or sneer at us
Mind you, you'll be limbless
Zazzorific!
Tell topsy turvy
Yell curvy scurvy
Rock and roll
Heart and soul
Split their ears, no matter
Scare them to scatter
Move aside
The second our brother steps in
It's like an atom bomb exploding
Hit the drum harder
Scare them to scatter
Master, coming
Movie aside
Bent double, sir?
- Where is the ID card?
- I have it, sir.
- First wear it, then go inside.
- Done.
We are all soaked in celebration mode.
Let's go.
Hey, hey, JD.
Hey, JD, come.
- Sit with us, JD.
- Is he a professor?
- Suspended professor.
- What is his name?
JD.
Start the program.
Sir, one minute.
Let me speak.
Sir--
Wait, dear.
I've attended
many college functions.
- Wear your ID card.
- Witnessed many gatherings.
But I've never seen a crowd like this.
Because the entire crowd here,
more than the host of the show,
is celebrating the man seated below.
It's not an ordinary thing.
If he is getting this kind of
reception among students,
then he must be a dedicated
and focused professor.
If he himself is like this,
- imagine his students.
- Why try all these gimmicks?
They must be as good as gold.
First give this man
a big round of applause.
To get a professor like him,
you and your college
must be truly blessed.
Your eyes are red, wear this shade.
He's the most revered master.
I want him to come up
to the dais and say a few words.
I'm talking to you, sir.
Please come.
Come up and speak.
Hey, where are you going?
Wait, let me tell a mini story.
Did you look at your shoes?
Instead of being humiliated, sit down.
- If you get up once more--
- What happened?
- Thank you.
- Please take your seat.
JD is our--
Management and staff
are completely against JD.
But students celebrate him.
I don't get this.
He has gone out of his way
to help students.
Students revere him as their true hero.
Reason enough for
the management to dislike him.
Secondly, after 6:00 p.m.,
our hero will be totally sloshed!
Good morning, sir.
- Hey.
- Careful, sir.
- Sorry, sorry.
- It's okay.
Hi, hi.
Your classroom is over there.
- Oh, good morning.
- Good morning.
Good morning.
What is his flashback sob story
to get sloshed every day?
Don't you ever ask him this.
If he gets a gullible idiot,
he'll reel off
a Mani Ratnam classic as his own!
Fell head over heels, followed her
wherever she went.
She also reciprocated and one day while
we were happily sitting in a coffee shop,
her father walked in!
- Did you get caught?
- Patience, Sister.
Her father's name
is Mr Chandramouli.
We were both neighbors
in Rainbow Colony.
I was in 8G.
She was in 7G.
India is here.
America is over there.
That's why I started playing guitar.
She was the love of my life.
We climbed up straight to
the top of the mountain.
We decided to jump
on the count of five.
My bad luck I got stuck
in a tree and escaped death.
What?
Her head hit a boulder and she died.
- That's a Kamal classic. Don't bug me
- Hey!
This is all too much.
Okay, which department is he in?
He studied in this very college.
He graduated in M.Phil Psychology.
Now he teaches Personality Development.
May I request you all to please stand up?
I said stand up.
Now I intend on checking
if your mind and body are focused.
We are hearing.
But not listening.
Students don't listen to their teachers.
Teachers don't listen to their students.
Now, run!
Run, run, run, run!
Water!
Electricity!
Children don't listen to their parents.
Parents don't listen to their children.
And finally,
...doesn't listen to their people.
Repeat whatever I tell you now verbatim
but do it the opposite way.
- Jump in!
- Jump left!
Jump right. Hey!
Now on the starboard.
Faster, faster, faster!
Now close your bloody eyes and freeze!
Class disperse.
Thank God.
I'm getting late for my class.
- We'll meet at lunch.
- Okay, sure.
Let me repeat this.
That bloody Bhavani is
responsible for all this.
He finished off his opponents contesting
in our Union Election one by one.
I know his history A to Z.
Gurumurthy, whether these people
understand it or not, hope you do.
I have been saying this
right from the beginning.
Who endorsed my view?
With the help of the juvenile delinquents,
he's engaging in criminal activities.
Has the cat got your tongue or what?
- Tell them.
- We've been saying the same--
Hello, sir.
Damn you!
Are you such a big shot, huh?
If you kill him, will you get his post?
- Let me see.
- No, Brother.
Why are you so mad at me?
I'm like a brother to you.
Whatever it is, let's talk it over.
Any need for me to talk to you?
I'm going to kill you.
Get the car ready.
Brother, will a problem
be solved if we fight?
Will murder solve the problem?
Let's discuss it amicably.
I'll use the same juvenile delinquents
you use as a tool to finish you off!
Wait and watch?
I grew up right before your eyes, sir.
- Wait, sir.
- You peed in your pants scared of me.
You think you're my equal now?
Whatever it is, let's talk it over.
I am much younger than you,
but pay heed to my words.
Don't go--
Oh, my God!
Gone.
Catch that lorry driver.
So sad.
You were eye witnesses.
What did I do?
If I had walked out talking to him,
I would've shared his fate.
Impossible for a human
to time this so perfectly.
I pray to all Gods thrice daily.
So God has saved me
and punished him.
He was a good soul!
To conduct students' election
in our college this year,
University Grants Commission has granted
permission, but I opposed it strictly.
That's why for a mere formality
I need all your opinions on
why we don't want the election.
For the records.
I somehow feel it is unnecessary, sir.
Semester is fast approaching.
In the current scenario,
why do we need an election?
Sir, if this happens, it will
create some other issue.
- I don't think they are fit for elections.
- Exactly.
In my honest opinion, no.
I have no issues with
the day college students.
I am a little apprehensive
about the evening batch.
Thanks, Ramya.
Charulatha, your opinion?
Sir, I joined the college
two weeks ago.
I don't know if it'd be right for me
to voice my opinion at the moment.
Come on, what's there?
- No, sir.
- Hey!
- Why is JD sir keeping quiet?
- That's right?
- He's waiting to make a good point.
- I don't think election is a good idea.
Sir, to be on the safe side,
ask JD his opinion.
JD, tell us your opinion.
What is your opinion, JD?
- What day was yesterday?
- Thursday.
Thursday is his day off.
- Professor JD.
- He would have been piss drunk.
- Come, come
- Hey, careful!
JD?
Sir!
Emergency, sir.
What are you doing here?
Let me give this phone to Rosie ma'am.
Her husband fell off his bike.
What the hell are you doing?
I will expel you.
- Let her just talk to him.
- What happened, Abdul?
Wake up, sir.
- Tell me!
- Don't switch off your phone.
Talk to him.
- Poor husband.
- One minute, sir.
They are objecting to elections.
Support us, sir.
- Sorry, sir.
- Get out!
- Useless fellow!
- Thank you, sir.
JD, what is your opinion
about conducting elections?
Election is essential. That's all.
- I knew it.
- He will say something meaningless, sir.
If we announce a students' election,
all of them will be thinking of only that.
None of them will study
nor will anyone attend any class.
Correct. What will they learn
by conducting students' election?
Why encourage politics in college?
Matthew sir.
What is politics, sir?
Sir, I don't wish to talk to you.
Is that so? But I wish to speak.
I'm coming.
Sir.
First, a student should know
politics means service.
Only if our students learn about election,
canvassing, leadership in college.
they will have an awareness about
state, central elections in the future.
College students are first time voters.
Only if they are allowed to think,
a new leader will emerge
for the next generation.
To be molded as a good leader
or to choose the right leader,
they will acquire
both tact and discretion.
- For someone to--
- Sir.
They will stick posters all over
and spoil the walls with graffiti.
Then claim ownership
over the walls and fight.
Doesn't all this happen
in normal elections?
Sit down, sir.
Aren't these things common in elections?
Can we abolish elections
in our country for this reason?
We have grown up with this culture of
poster, banner and still follow it.
For students to know
the do's and don'ts with posters,
we must conduct
elections in college.
Only then they will
do well in the outside world.
If our culture of bribing with biriyani
booze and big bucks should change,
students should know
the in and out of politics.
Okay.
Let's assume what you're saying is right.
Who is responsible if students resort
to violence or damage college property?
Sir, nothing of that sort will happen.
If you are proved wrong,
will you leave this college?
Will you resign, huh?
I'll think about it if it happens.
Then you be the presiding officer
and conduct the election.
If any problem crops up,
you have to leave the college.
Give this in writing.
Coming June 25th
Students' elections.
I haven't seen him conduct
an election as a master.
But I've seen him
do the same as a student.
Shake your hands.
This is the wall of democracy.
Your rules and regulations.
Gym facilities free for all students.
Meat will be served for all in the hostel.
Good orators have become able leaders.
You should speak up more boldly, Savi.
Instead of finding faults
with your rival,
ask for votes
listing your reforms.
Tear every single poster, dude.
Posters and banners should be stuck
or erected in their allocated places.
Even if there's a small brawl
among the students,
election will be canceled.
You pull back and fire.
Cheers!
Our total strength is 5500 students, sir.
We have divided them into 10 categories.
What is this column?
That is the religion and caste category.
Let's avoid that.
We have to remove this from here
to ensure it doesn't follow us
wherever we go.
How much longer do you intend on
drinking and loitering around?
Why yell at me for no reason?
Will I yell at you
if you are steady on your feet?
- I am sober.
- Is that so?
Hit an arrow
anywhere on this board.
I'll agree you are sober and steady.
Dude, aim for the bull's eye.
One lakh rupees to students
in each department.
Cheers!
- Cheers.
I have a fair amount of
experience in counselling.
If you can tell me the reason,
I can do my level best to help you.
You know, when I was jobless,
I hanged around
a tiles company in Rajasthan.
- Oh!
- At that time,
a girl lost her bag in the train.
I found it and sent it to her.
She liked me for the effort I took.
She and I became pen pals
and we fell in love
then when she knew
I was in Rajasthan.
For my sake, that girl knitted
an embroidered sweater for me
and sent it to me.
Sweater in Rajasthan!
True.
Tomorrow if you have a problem
and you come to me,
even if it's midnight,
I'll be there for you.
Why should we create problems
and end up in the police station?
Beverages free in the canteen.
Aqua training access free.
You will have campus interviews.
You'll leave the college
with a job in hand.
Above all give this a serious thought.
Do you want to be ruled by a girl?
Or revel in a boy's leadership?
Hey, that isn't even my glass.
Some other chap had relished
his drink and is gone you madcap!
How dare you!
One JD, please.
The third round of votes
have been counted.
We have started counting
for the fourth round.
Sir?
Fourth round, sir.
Results are due any moment.
I'm scared, sir.
Are you Satyaraj acting
as Amavasai in Amaidhi Padai?
"Fourth round!"
Get lost.
Most awaiting election results
are going to be declared very soon.
Fourth and final election results
are going to be declared.
Bhargav 2588 votes.
Savitha 2648 votes.
Savitha won the election by 60 votes.
Congratulations, Chairperson.
Sir, I think they have already
started creating a ruckus there.
Sir, what do we do now?
Why do you still ask me?
She's the captain of your ship.
Chairman, tell us what to do?
Sir...
To avoid all these unnecessary confusion,
I'm thinking of talking
to Bhargav in person.
Look at that!
By all means go and talk.
But go alone.
Madam.
Don't dilly-dally, scratch your head,
crack your knuckles and keep looking back.
Don't dawdle and
do instalment walk.
Forward march!
Sir, will you give me your bracelet?
Why?
- Please give, sir.
- Dude, play that song.
Look! We must lead a life like that bird
Without a care in the world
We should go on a dancing spree
Like the waves here in glee
Under the same sky spacious
On the same land so precious
Under the same sky endless
On our Motherland peerless
I want to talk to you.
If she comes offering a truce,
I'll break the bones on her face.
- Sir, tell me.
- What happened?
Your son lost, sir.
What?
Bhargav...
I came to congratulate.
Winning by just 60 votes
is no big victory at all.
Is there any rule in college
there should be only one chairman?
You take over day college
and I'll handle evening college.
Okay, bye.
Congrats.
I extended my hand
even on nomination day,
but you weren't in the mood to shake.
At least let there be truce now?
I don't think it's safe
for her to go alone.
Shall I go and check, sir?
Let's shake hands.
- Okay.
- How ridiculous.
He has patched up happily.
He is shaking hands
with that girl who won.
Let me talk to him.
One minute, sir.
Bhargav.
Dad, there's no problem.
I spoke to that girl.
She even asked me to be
the chairman for day college, Dad.
You got a sudden desire to
beg a post from her, huh?'
It isn't what you think, Dad.
I'll explain it to you in person.
- Sir.
- Pack him home in our car now.
Okay, sir.
If he refuses to go, threaten him.
- Rough up that female who defeated him.
- I'll handle it.
I'll explain to my dad.
Please don't create a ruckus.
He has given me permission
to scar even your face, sir.
First, get inside.
But please don't hurt that girl.
Sir, he wasn't nasty to me.
I shook hands and he said okay.
That's all.
Celebrations are done.
- Hey! Catch.
- Sir.
Wear those IDs.
- Where's the booth?
- First floor, sir.
Hurry up.
Clear up all this mess
and then rock and roll.
Sir, evening college students are
planning to burn down the booth.
- Who is he?
- Professor, sir.
- What?
- That wasn't a proper election.
- We demand re-election or re-counting.
- Election is over. That's it.
- Burn down the booth.
- Which department are you?
- Come here.
- Stop this bloody idle talk.
I'll kill you, son of a gun
I'll break all your teeth!
- Sri, quiet!
- Give that bottle.
- Wait.
- Sir!
- Sir, let go of me!
- Shut up, all of you.
I'm trying to make peace-
Sir, move aside!
Evening college chairman candidate
Bhargav wants to talk to you, sir.
My dad didn't listen to me.
He has sent about 60 party riff-raffs
to bash up everyone in the college.
They have merged with the students.
Ensure our college students are safe.
On the starboard!
- Why are all of them spinning?
- What are they doing?
Now close your bloody eyes and freeze!
What is this? Tell us, sir.
Sticking to the wall like glue?
Move forward.
They are doing the opposite.
Wait, don't go.
Send all the girls home safe.
- Sir?
- Just do as I say.
Hey! Take all of them
through the back door.
Go, go, fast!
Go now!
Savitha, you go!
Hey! That's the girl.
Grab her!
Savitha.
Hey!
Are you okay?
Go in. Quick.
Sir, students are all out of control.
Let me go.
- Take your hands off.
- Let go of me. Sir.
Take your hands off!
How dare you manhandle girls!
Master!
Nothing major, just a nail scratch.
Meeting is being held in the library.
Is everyone safe?
I have checked with all the groups.
They have texted me.
The entire riot has been recorded
in our college CCTV cameras.
Is he behaving like a professor?
Excuse me, ma'am, you are only
talking about damage of property.
Rowdies got together and
bashed up about five of our girls.
What could all the teachers do?
- No one came to stop them.
- Stop it, Charu.
You haven't even completed
a month in the college.
Just keep quiet.
What the hell are they discussing?
I'll be back.
I'll talk to JD.
Then we will take a call.
If he comes back,
we will resign, sir.
- No, Mr. Samuel-
- What's going on here?
Sir, I have already given
a commitment that I'll resign.
I'm just leaving this college.
JD, just wait in the car.
- I need to talk to you.
- Sir?
I said wait.
I understand.
If they need to know your worth,
a gap is essential.
Your decision is correct.
You wanted a break
for three months, right?
I have okayed it.
When did I ask?
Isn't this your signature?
Sir.
Carbon copy, sir.
Oh! Come on, JD.
Haven't you opted for three months
break to teach?
Teach? In which college?
College?
You have mentioned
Observation Home.
Sir, don't play with me.
What will I do there?
I didn't sign this.
Maybe after 6:00 p.m.?
After 6:00 p.m.,
there's a possibility.
See.
JD, you're losing control on yourself.
If there's any issue in the election,
didn't you agree to resign your job?
That means you had
something on your mind.
Fine, sir, I'll go.
Well, I've many well-wishers here.
They must be behind this.
It's okay, I need a change too, I'll go.
Inspector is waiting in your lodge
to explain the job you'll be undertaking.
That means.
- Needhimani.
- Sir?
You didn't pass on any information?
No, sir.
Then whatever lawyer
and I spoke in the union office,
- How did the police get to hear?
- That's what puzzles me, sir.
You know this music director Anirudh?
He has composed a new film song.
Shall we listen?
- Listen.-Sir...
Bhavani has fixed the date.
You are his next target.
He has decided to kill you too.
What do you say now, bigamist?
At least is this your voice
or will you claim it's mimicry?
- Sir.
- Did you call me, Bhavani?
Make sure the boys are supplied
their regular dose of drinks and drugs.
Whether they get
three square meals a day or not,
booze and dope should flow steadily.
Okay, Bhavani. I'll see to it.
- Where was I?
- Sir.
You got me married. How
can you make my wife a widow?
- Tell me, sir.
- Wait.
I'm choking with emotion
hearing your sentimental speech.
Stop moving like that, will you?
I had tucked the knife in my waist.
What if it pierces me in the wrong place?
- Sir.
- Suppose an enemy kills us,
doesn't matter if they say
that's how Bhavani died a noble death.
If they say he had tucked a knife
that stabbed him in a wrong spot,
does that sound good?
- No.
- No, right?
Won't sound good.
- Lean back comfortably.
- Don't, sir.
- Do you really respect me?
- Yes, sir.
How come over the phone
all this kinship was missing?
What is this?
- Lean back.
- No, sir.
Won't you listen to what I'm saying?
Lean back. Sit, sit, sit!
Lean back!
Gopal!
- Hey.
- Yes, sir.
Tell me, sir.
Ask Das to pick two boys
10, 15 years old to surrender.
- Okay, sir.
- Go.
Sir?
A new master has been recruited
for our reformatory.
- Okay. So?
- I didn't know if you knew.
So I thought I should inform you.
A teacher is bound to be appointed.
All of you are giving a build up
as if it is breaking news!
Dispose this body and
ask someone to drive this truck.
Okay, sir.
Creep like a lioness, make no sound
Slide like a snake over sun baked ground
Sir, can we switch off that cacophony.
Then shall I wear my coolers?
Twist like a hurricane, bend and sway
Break like a wave, wash the filth away
Sir, college students are bound by
certain protocols of parents and society,
but those boys
lack all that discipline.
Their age and their activities
have no connection whatsoever.
Not even a single inmate
is human or humane.
Beasts.
- Kabaddi.-Demons.
Kabaddi.
They know our law is lenient
to their habitual crimes.
They use it to their advantage
breaking laws like reckless criminals.
That's why, I'm telling you, sir.
Don't bend backwards to reform them
in these three months
you are assigned there.
Aren't you wondering
whether to go there or not?
Sir?
Sir!
Is our hero in dream world?
Sir, check if that's your phone?
Sir.
Wake up, sir.
Not mine.
Oh! It's his phone.
That's no problem, sir.
I don't mind going.
- I can handle them.
- Sir.
So have you decided to go?
Here.
Das.
That teacher will be here tomorrow.
Despite knowing about this place,
he is ready to set foot here.
Don't underestimate him.
Let him land.
After he steps in here,
let's see if he lasts here
even for half an hour.
You should be in there
by 10 o'clock.
If you freshen up,
I can take you in my car.
In that the vehicle?
- Yes.
- Okay, you go.
- I'll take you safe--
- I'll shower and come.
Okay, sir.
You don't like it here, don't you?
Three months.
If he comes in
and starts teaching,
ask all of them
to fling these at him.
Das.
Oh yeah
You know who it is!
If I'm doin' somethin'
Boy... I like to do it well
And when I'm in the zone
Ain't nobody stoppin' me
Oh yeah
You know who it is
Das, look at his stride and beard!
Doesn't look like a master.
Doesn't carry a book or a cane.
He looks so local.
We'll provoke him and then pounce.
Oh yeah
Master
They call me master
You know me master
I'm master the blaster
Oh yeah
Master
They call me master
You know me master
I'm master the blaster
If you step foot in our place
It is trespassing into our space
We will hassle you to the root
Master, change your route
As juveniles we roam
In this Observation Home
Tears in our eyes ready
If you ask us to study
Don't take lessons in life
Or ask us to drop our knife
Your lame advice is of no use
We don't want your views
Sir, don't take lessons in life-
Why did you stop singing?
It was such a peppy song.
Wow!
Song. Sketches.
You look like a bunch of talented boys.
Not bad at all.
Are you setting out to play?
Why? What's wrong?
I don't interfere in the likes
or dislikes of anyone, boss.
Whoever wants to play, go ahead.
Want to sit here, be my guest.
I am allergic to the sun.
I'll sit right here.
Should I teach now?
- No, no.
- We want to play.
Very good.
- I must catch up on Amazon, Netflix.
- Shall we give the letter now, Brother?
I hate the sight of
this classroom, bench.
- I will throw all this out.
- Not now, I'll tell you.
Don't indulge in all this graffiti
on the board, bathroom walls.
You focus on your work
and I'll stick to my job.
Deal?
We thought of chasing you away
if you started lessons today.
You are unique, Master.
He seems to be one of us.
Turns out I don't have to do anything.
Why waste time sitting?
Why is this place so dirty
and stinking to high heaven?
We celebrate 10 festivals a year
and 20 birthdays of leaders.
You don't clean up this place
and celebrate on any occasion?
What is celebrate?
That means--
Having a blast, huh?
Right.
Rock on.
We have no idea of day or date.
You and your ideas!
So simple.
Some of you were singing
when I entered, right?
- Who were they?
- I sang.
Four of you sang, right?
If 40 of you sing in chorus,
that's celebration.
Come with me.
I'll show you.
Beat it.
Let me sing a short story
Pay attention, listen to me
Why singing in English, sir?
Just listen, Brother.
Let me sing a short story
Pay attention, listen to me
If you want, take it or else
No need tension, leave it, baby
Life is very short, buddy
Always be happy
Hundreds of problems will come and go
Chill a bit, bro
Together, man.
Let me sing a short story
Pay attention, listen to me
If you want, take it or else
No tension, leave it, baby
Life is very short, buddy
Always be happy
Hundreds of problems will come and go
Chill a bit, bro
No tension, baby.
If you race at a zip zap zoom speed
Concentration is a must indeed
If you crawl at a slow pace
To be steady is a must always
Oh! Anger always misery, baby
Stand united as friends, powerful, buddy
Haters are gonna hate but ignore calmly
Delete negativity totally, baby
Focus on what you dream
and don't worry, bro
Positivity will lift you, baby
Life is very short, buddy
Always be happy
Very many problems will come and go
Don't be tense, chill a bit, bro
Students.
Let me sing a short story
Pay attention, listen to me
If you want, take it or else
no need tension, leave it, baby
Life is very short, buddy
Always be happy
Hundreds of problems will come and go
Chill a bit, bro
No tension, baby.
Hard work too is necessary
Smart work also is compulsory
Self-motivation
Isn't it your reflection?
You need education
Plus total dedication
Try self-evaluation
for validation
Don't be the person spreading hatred, bro
To talk behind one's back is so crappy
Always be polite and just don't be nasty
You be the reason to make someone happy
Life is very short, buddy
Always be happy
Many problems will come and go
Put your feet up, bro
One last time.
Let me sing a short story
Pay attention, listen to me
If you want, take it or else
No need tension, leave it, baby
Life is very short, buddy
Always be happy
Hundreds of problems will come and go
Chill a bit, bro
That was my short story
How was my short story?
Go, go, go.
Master.
He's asleep.
Wake him up now.
Sir.
Sir?
- Put the letter in his pocket.
- He is sleeping, Brother.
Just do it.
Hey!
Who is that tickling me?
I can hear footsteps, we'll talk
to him over the phone tonight.
Come away.
We shouldn't get caught.
Thank God, only another 89 days left.
Go home.
Hello, stop.
I noticed it just now.
Don't know who played this prank.
Why are you riding a cycle?
I can drop you in my car.
That's alright. I can manage--
I was hoping at least
you will bring about a change.
Why? It's all going smooth.
The boys are having fun.
We are submerged in problems.
Half the boys are drowning
in a sea of drugs.
Whatever they get
they readily use as weapons.
Everyday some boy or the other
twists his arm or ankle.
Why tell me all these tales?
Am I the police or what?
I'm just a teacher here.
Sir, you don't understand.
The police will nab the criminals.
Court will punish them.
To guide these boys,
to sift and sieve right from wrong,
we are not equipped, sir.
They need a master like you.
First, understand this is
a reformatory for juvenile delinquents.
The boys have got into a fist-fight, sir.
I am unable to control them
Whoever is out there, come in, sir.
Wait, man. I'm coming in now.
First, close A block and
ensure outsiders don't enter.
He isn't picking the phone.
What happened, Brother?
I tried 10-15 times.
He isn't picking my call.
Try again, Brother.
He isn't picking our call.
Do you remember Sister Charu's number?
Call her, Brother.
Hurry up.
Manikandan speaking, Sister.
You saw me in the Observation Home.
Someone is coming.
- Switch off the phone.-Hello, hello?
Can you hear me, Mani?
- Let's go.
- Go, Brother.
Enjoy the biriyani.
Sir.
- We don't want.
- Why?
Not hungry.
Is that so?
He asked you to eat, right?
Half-baked nutcase!
How much I have suffered
starving in a place like this?
Get me some water.
Sir, I'm scared--
Lucky to get a leg piece in biriyani.
You can even kill someone,
but not rob him of their food.
Go on, eat.
Water.
Enough.
They took my phone though
they knew very well it was mine.
Whom did you call?
No one, sir.
Don't know.
Tell me the truth.
I don't know, sir.
Ma... master, sir.
Who?
The master who joined duty.
- Master, huh?
- He's a boozer, sir.
You don't have to take him
seriously at all, sir.
Why, master?
My father died
when I was a kid.
Couldn't bear the hunger,
I stole and got caught.
They piled cases on me.
And sent me to this
Ju... Juvenile Home, sir.
We are being released tomorrow.
But he is asking me to surrender
for a murder case, sir.
If my mother gets to know this,
she will die of shock, sir.
If you had called me
instead of calling that master,
I'm emotional by nature you see,
I would have told
someone else to surrender.
Not wanting to surrender
isn't a mistake on your part,
but you wanted to sneak out
our internal information.
Isn't that a grave mistake?
Grown-up boy, you tell me
what you did was wrong or not?
- Yes, it was wrong.
- So I am right?
Enough of eating biriyani.
I'll take it. You've had enough.
Here, take this.
Aren't we both very young, sir?
Think of us as your younger brother
and please forgive us this time.
My dear, only boys like you
should not be pardoned.
They pardoned me.
Look how it has shaped me.
How do we deal with this?
We won't repeat this, sir.
We won't snitch to anyone.
Well...
Listen, you can be scared
of anyone in this world
but if death knocks at our door,
even if it is Lord Yama,
you shouldn't be scared.
I'll give you two minutes.
Kill me and then save
your brother and yourself.
What were you doing
when these kids stole your phone?
On top of it, you have
this stuck up attitude!
- Go away.
- I won't leave you.
Listen to me.
Just run away.
- Run outside.
- I won't go.
You mess up everything.
Only plus is your voice!
- Go!
- I won't.
You have only one minute left.
Decide fast.
Go away from here.
I won't leave you alone.
What are you doing?
This is what I expected from you!
Clear out.
I won't leave you.
Brother!
Wake up, sir. Get up.
I'm constable Arumugam.
Get up, sir.
School starts only at 10 o'clock.
Why are you waking me--
We have a problem on hand.
Inspector wants to see you.
- Hurry up!
- Why should I meet the inspector?
You have to get up now.
There's a big problem.
Okay, I'll get up.
Don't shake me up like a rattle!
Go, I'll follow.
I will come.
Start... make it quick.
If delinquents like us lament in pain
Will our voice be heard or is it in vain?
Not too sure, sir.
I think they were here
for less than a year.
Two innocent boys here
Lost their lives so dear
To reside here or hang by a rope
One and the same without hope
What are you gawking at, huh?
Hey! Who are you?
- Get out.
- Sir, sir.
He is our class master.
Oh! You are that master, huh?
First I have to interrogate you.
What did you do?
This has never happened before.
Did you hit any of the boys?
Tell me.
Can't you hear me?
Answer me, man.
Sir, what is this?
Not here, I need to
take him for inquiry.
- Get him into our police jeep.
- Come, sir.
Search all the rooms in case
they left any suicide note.
We want to reform given a choice
We are good-for-nothing boys
If delinquents like us lament in pain
Will our voice be heard or is it in vain?
If good-for-nothing louts wail
Will our voice make justice prevail?
N2 POLICE STATION
VADASERI
Bhavani, can we come with you?
He has asked me to come
alone, I can handle it.
What about that master
who is in the police custody?
I came out of the reformatory
15 years ago.
The reason I've been patient
for the past five years is
because I want to kill
these three men
and become the president
of the drivers' union.
Two men are dead and gone.
He's the only one left.
He wants to see me.
Is he my priority?
Or is this master important?
He's important.
- What shall we do with this master?
- I'll handle him.
- Sure?
- No problem.
- Shall I go now?
- Okay. I'll go too.
Let's go.
Come with me.
Where are you going?
- Two minutes, sir.
- Quick. Sir will be here anytime.
Are you the mother of
those two boys who died?
- Yes, sir.
- Is that so?
Give him all the details--
You are completely drunk, right?
- Sit outside.
- Okay, sir.
If someone is calling you
ten times from the same number,
won't it occur to you that
there may be a serious problem?
No, Ch... Charu.
Why do you look blank?
I was a volunteer in an NGO
before I took up this post here.
Based on a complaint, I went to
inspect the Observation Home.
That's how I befriended those two boys.
They told me about the injustice
in that reformatory.
But I couldn't take
any legal action.
So many vile threats.
The only reason I shifted to Chennai
was to handle such cases myself.
I needed to be financially secure.
So I took up this lecturer's post.
When you defended the students,
my faith was recharged.
I was convinced this flawed system
could be changed for the better.
I forged your signature for this post.
I was the one who applied
for this job on your behalf.
Even the founder is aware of this.
Now I feel that was a big mistake.
If you hadn't come here,
at least those two boys would be alive.
Now both of them have left us.
How can you defend yourself, sir?
See, I had no idea whatsoever.
No one told me anything.
When have you been
sober enough to understand?
Have you ever realized anytime
who is talking to you?
I have my share of personal problems.
I am unable to come out of it.
I can't...
...cry.
I can't cry, I can't sleep
at night either, that's why
I drink.
I swear I never thought
it would be this horrific.
Oh! You can never cry, right?
I can't understand.
Tell me without crying.
Charu, where are you--
- Were your boys into drugs?
- I never thought I would see them dead.
This is the lady who gave birth
to those boys who are dead now.
I had reassured her.
A master will come.
He will save your boys.
Both my sons were very fond of each other.
They were inseparable.
My eldest told me
this just last week.
Let my younger brother study,
I'll find some job to support us.
A master was coming he said.
He was sure they will be rescued.
But no one came.
My entire lineage has snapped.
Where are you?
Hurry up.
Listen to him.
Bring your wife.
- Come here.
- You can go.
He has gone back to his old ways.
- Sir.
- Who are they?
She is master's colleague
from the college.
Pack them all off and
move that master to the cell.
Okay, sir.
Clear the other cases
out of the station.
Okay, sir.
What will I do now?
How will I live without them?
You're still unable
to shed tears even?
Your eyes won't shed tears
till the day you die.
Get even more sloshed.
Why are you lamenting here?
Shut up now.
I said shut up.
Do I have to repeat myself?
Clear this place now, madam.
Clear out.
Come with me, sir.
I swear--
Come along, sir.
Standing rooted to the spot.
- I swear I didn't expect any of this.
- Remember this.
Don't forget you are also responsible
for the death of those two boys.
Convey my apologies to their mother.
You are taking undue advantage
of the respect I'm giving you.
Don't make me lose my temper.
Stand right there.
Go in.
I sacrificed my children
in such an awful unjust way.
Hey! Come here.
Sir, please light an incense stick.
There are mosquitoes here.
Go inside.
Listen, Bhavani.
Only you and I are left to contest
the Lorry Drivers' Union election.
I have to win unopposed.
Looks like it may rain.
Can we have tea
and then discuss?
Master, my name is Sabari.
My elder brother is Manikandan.
He stole from a bakery for my sake
because I was starving.
But they foisted some other case
on us and brought us here.
Everything is wrong here, master.
They thrash us mercilessly.
They stuff some powder into our mouths.
Immediately even our teeth
start shivering, Master.
Don't know if it is day or night.
We put up with all this
thinking it is for a short period.
Now when we are
about to be released,
they want us to surrender
for some other murder case.
Otherwise, they are threatening
to kill our mother, Master.
Sister Charu assured that us
you will come and rescue us.
Please save us, Master.
Our poor mother.
She is all alone.
My eyes have dried up out of crying.
I can't cry anymore, Master.
Please, Brother.
Rescue us from this hell.
I am begging you, Brother.
Go ahead.
I told you, Bhavani.
I want to win unopposed.
I called you here
to arrive at a compromise.
But I can't trust you.
You'll take any kind of cruel measure
using those juvenile delinquents.
Should I step out of my house daily
with fear and breathe in fear?
That is why--
Did you call me here
planning to kill me?
You--
You call someone
with a plan to kill him.
Treat him royally like a guest
and offer him hot tea.
You're the only man who
asked for my permission to kill me.
Instead you could have--
Putting you on a pedestal, I wanted to
fix an auspicious day to finish you off.
I need my brain examined!
Hey! Wait.
I'll give you two minutes.
Kill me and then save
your men and yourself.
Hurry up.
Do you need an army
to bash up one man?
Open the door first.
Hey, he is a teacher.
Watch your blows.
You've got only ten minutes.
Come out without too much damage.
Turn the other way.
Come, Murali.
Switch it off and come.
Pray to God you don't
run into me in your next life.
Don't, Bhavani.
Wonder what their plan is!
Master, my boss has
given you a bus ticket.
Luxury bus.
Air-conditioned sleeper.
Leave tonight, you'll reach
your hometown in the morning.
Got it into your head?
If you stubbornly refuse,
you saw the two boys
hanging from the roof, right?
You'll be next.
I'm talking to you.
Is that a love letter in your hand?
Sabari, Manikandan.
These two boys refused to surrender,
and they ended up dead--
Sir, it's too loud!
Ignore, we'll handle it later.
Sir, the noise is ear-splitting.
- Go in and check.
- Okay.
Stab and rip him apart.
Sir?
They may kill that master.
Please come here, sir.
Soundar! Open the door.
Open the damn door.
Soundar.
- Tell me.
- Bhavani!
The master--
Who are you?
Who is behind this?
What is your motive?
Why do you use these innocent boys?
I don't know any of this.
But I will find out.
I'll search for the men
framing the innocent boys
for their crimes.
I'll hunt high and low, find you
and stand right in front of you.
I will--
I will make you pay
for the death of these two boys.
Master.
There's nothing new
in whatever I'm about to say.
But I'll say it anyway
and you listen.
I'm waiting!
I will meet you face to face!
He stands for powerful victory
Who is he?
Thalapathy!
Das, I'm very scared.
He is back again.
Is there no one to save me?
Oh, no...
Don't spoil for a fight unnecessarily
If you give us hell foolhardily
a stone will split your skull speedily
Master, you've been staring
at the rope for a long time?
Want to swing on it?
What is that famous song of his?
Let me tell a short story
No, it's not short,
a sad story.
Let me tell a sad story
Zip lip or slip
Skip and trip
Chill a little, bro
Hey, Master!
Youths to the youngest ones
are doped day and night, Brother.
When they are intoxicated,
they are not in control of their senses.
Both have plenty of
criminal cases against them.
Two boys who died are sheer poison.
Both must have died
when totally tanked, sir.
They won't toe the line with
their parents or with our rules.
They are arrogant boys
who insist their word is the law.
There are 10-12 years old
with all kinds of diseases in them.
All dazed and doped.
Who told you they were
good-for-nothing boys?
Both were 24 carat gold, sir.
Those two boys
called up a girl I know
on the night they died.
You mean, Charu?
Yes, Charu.
I know Charu and I know
who killed those two boys too.
We have tried our level best.
But we are unable to stop
the dope and booze supply.
How can drugs enter the premises
without your knowledge, sir?
They have so many routes to supply, sir.
Without the wardens' support
nothing can be brought in, sir.
As per our rule book, you can't
touch the boys below 18 here.
Using that as an excuse,
they are crossing the line.
These rogues are taking advantage
of the fear instilled in everyone's minds.
These poor kids! Trapped for life
caught in Bhavani's web
Who is Bhavani?
Beast!
- Bhava... Bhavani?
- I don't know anyone by that name.
Sir, stop pestering us
with your questions.
If you've got any other work,
carry on, okay?
See you, sir.
Let's go.
Teachers who came here earlier
to reform these boys,
would have made a hasty retreat
thinking their family takes priority.
But my story is completely different.
I have no one to call my own, sir.
The day I saw those boys'
corpses hanging,
their eyes bulging,
tongues sticking out,
I died, sir.
If you help me,
I can change this place.
I'm ready to face any hardship.
I don't care even if I lose my life.
My life's breath
I have no problem, sir.
If you stick to the rules and regulations,
even move heaven and earth legally,
I will back you up hundred percent, sir.
High time I stop needing a high from you
Enough of tumbling thanks to you!
Today my troubled times will heal anew
Enough of being sloshed night and day
Get it out of your system today
Enough of gifting yourself strife
Switch off this dizzying life
No more booze to give a kick
Quit now, double quick
Break the bottles, you surely should
Trash them for your own good
Enough of being sloshed night and day
Get it out of your system today
Forgive me.
No more booze to give a kick
Quit now, double quick
Break the bottles, you surely should
Trash them for your own good
Enough of being sloshed night and day
Get it out of your system today
Enough of gifting yourself strife
Switch off this dizzying life
Enough of being sloshed night and day
Get it out of your system today
Break the bottles, you surely should
Trash them for your own good
You got me wrong, Bhavani.
Ever since Gurumurthy died,
everyone is scared
to contest for that post.
I've spoken to the district councillor.
In another 10 days,
it will be announced
that you won unopposed.
Come here.
Brother, she is the one
putting a spoke in the wheel.
She's the one who registered the case.
Our boys sent her photo just now.
What should we do with her?
Can't you handle a female?
As if you need a priest to choose
an auspicious time! Get lost!
Bhavani, even if someone else
occupies this post as a union leader,
he is going to take orders from you.
Then why aspire for this post?
Fear stemming out of murder is short lived,
but fear derived from a post of power
and authority lasts a lifetime, right?
After this I'm entering politics.
I don't know how many more I'd have
to kill to make my dream come true.
- I'm not following you, Bhavani.
- Everything...
Our boys will shoulder the sin.
They call me master
Changes will happen faster
Hey, Master!
- He looks like a groom, doesn't he?
- Correct, man.
He looks different, right?
Master is in a mood
to teach us a lesson.
Do you think he's married?
If he was married
and if his wife looks hot
super, right?
All of you stand height-wise.
Shorter ones in the front.
Taller ones in the back.
Come on, fast.
Do you think you can scare
us with this new look of yours?
- Move on to your next job.
- At least pretend to be scared.
Poor master!
Let me repeat.
Fall in line.
Stand height-wise.
Master, don't judge a book by its cover.
Instead of height try weight as a measure.
This chap like a buffalo here.
Pickpocket case.
Real pipsqueak.
But our little black ant
had the guts to kill.
A cut above the rest.
Then isn't he the heaviest?
What is your name?
You heard me?
Master, you can't lay a finger on us.
You know that, right?
Sir, you can't lay a finger on the boys.
Rules.
Don't hit them and
get caught unnecessarily.
Like a new starched shirt,
he's all stiff and spruced up.
Master's raid begins
A-Aa-E-Ee, A-B-C-D
This is our time, buddy
Come, brother, welcome
It is wrong only if I bash up the boys?
Yes.
Why are you beating me?
Stop beating us!
If you come in to commit a crime
Master's raid will give you a hard time
It hurts, sir!
Sir, please don't.
Why are you hitting us?
You think you can hit us
just because you are a teacher?
We are wardens here.
We told you not to hit the boys.
But why are you hitting us.
Don't run over him
And look the other way
Don't get into his bad books,
stay away
Master's raid, no warranty
Pain 100% guarantee
It hurts, sir.
Please don't hit.
Sir, I'm going to Sabarimala.
Why? What happened to your devotion
when you were peddling drugs?
Sir, stop hitting us.
Who is the master?
Commander!
24 carat gold is he
Lion king royalty
Move aside
Watch his stride
Shut the gate tight
- Name?
- Bharath.
- Sibi.
- Karuppusami.
- Dhanus.
- Udaya.
- Venkatesh.
- Stephen.
Pencil.
It's an inspection.
All of you line up to one side.
He will take law into his hand
When discipline fails to stand
Master's raid will be well planned
When he uses his soft voice
Obey his rules, dear boys
If you defy however slight
His cane will hug you tight
Don't create a ruckus
His warning smile is dangerous
Accept your mistake, Brother.
He will let you go
Good boy!
What was that noise, lad?
Your nose is bleeding bad
Wherever you hide, dude
Master's eyes will find you
Listen to master's advice
You'll be wealthy and wise
If you act smart anymore
Time to kneel on the floor
Don't stand and stare
Don't get caught again, beware
Hit him once, you are out cold
He will retaliate multifold
Don't turn a blind eye
To a crime on the roadside
Says 'Thirukkural' wisely
Don't chicken out and flee
My followers devotedly
Will be true wholeheartedly
Without discrimination
Of caste, race, religion
Apple of our eye is our nation
We were patient till now
But we will retaliate, World war
Continents will quake and quiver
Nonentities will shake and shiver
His entry spells power
Loud and clear
Who is he?
Thalapathy
24 carat gold is he
Lion king royalty
Move aside, dude
Beast mode
Master, my name is Sabari.
My brother's name is Manikandan.
My brother stole from
a bakery for my sake
But they foisted another case-
Bhavani, that master is
acting too big for his boots.
He bashed up the wardens.
He raided the premises and burnt
all the drugs, dopes and phones.
What to do with him now?
How did a master get to be so gutsy?
Find out who is backing him up.
Let's get to work.
Don't stand and stare
Don't get caught again, beware
Hit him once, you are out cold
He will retaliate multifold
Won't turn a blind eye
To a crime on the roadside
My dear angels!
Can you give us a hand?
Without discrimination
Of caste, race, religion
Love, huh?
Apple of our eye is our nation
We were patient till now
Reign of terror, World war 3
Continents will quake and quiver
Nonentities will shake and shiver
Master spells power
Take your hands off.
24 carat gold is he
Lion king royalty
Move aside, dude
Beast mode
Master, you had your way?
You can trim my hair
or tonsure my head.
Beware of my leader Undiyal.
Try your tricks on him.
Undiyal, listen to me.
- Don't go there, go to your block.
- Shut up, Warden.
- Good morning, Boss.
- Morning.
Who had the guts to
lay a finger on our hair?
Is there a rule about
the length of the hair?
Master, do you know the rules or not?
You are having a free hand
with everyone's heads.
Master.
Let go of me, Master.
You don't know who
you're laying your hands on.
You will regret what you're doing.
Master's raid
Pain post-paid
Don't get into strife
Run for your life
Don't do it.
I'm scared.
- Hey, Dheena.
- Sir.
- Let it be a close cut.
- Yes, sir.
Don't run over him
And look the other way
Don't get into his bad books
Stay away
Master's raid
All crimes waylaid
A-Aa-E-Ee, A-B-C-D
This is our time, buddy
Brother, good morning
Master's raid in full swing
Next week will be
back to square one.
You can come back
and scrub it again, okay?
Bye, Sweetheart.
I've never seen such bad
nicotine stains at such an young age, JD.
Prise open their mouth
it's like a cigarette shop!
I have collected cavity samples
from the six boys you mentioned.
- How long will it take?
- I'll let you know in one or two days.
Thanks, Madhi.
He left me with a half shaved
moustache and beard.
Such a disgrace!
I feel like I am naked!
I'm so mad I want to kill him right now.
In this dirty business,
enemies will come and go.
If we rage like a mad bull against every
single enemy, our life will be ruined.
Handle him with patience.
Make him run in all four directions.
Don't let him sleep.
- Torture him mentally.
- Fine.
- Hey--
- I'll tackle him.
Hey! Come out.
Listen to me.
I'm telling you boys.
Wait.
- What happened?
- Sir, I don't know.
They just started a brawl
and started hitting each other.
Back door is open in A block.
What to do now?
Go look for the key.
Hurry up.
Quick, man.
Don't let anyone out.
Lock them up in the class.
- Okay, sir.
- Give me the torch.
You'll get bashed up.
Get lost!
Hello, sir.
- Yes, tell me.
- None of our boys are missing I hope.
No, sir, the head count is 63.
Not one of them is missing.
They came from outside for sure.
It's burning!
Oh, God!
You're hurting me.
Bala!
What happened to you?
You messed up my face, right?
Go, collect your mess.
- This is just the beginning, master?
- Look at this, Master.
Hit them at least once, Master.
Hey master! This is your fate
every single minute you are here.
Don't think this is the end.
There's more to come.
We will escape from here tonight.
Stop us if you can.
I was on my bike
sticking to the kerb side.
Whether he collided by mistake
or deliberately targeted me,
only God knows.
But his intention is to provoke you.
He wants you to lose your cool
and raise your hand on those boys.
So that the authorities can move
you someplace else.
Don't act rashly on impulse.
Only his leg is fractured.
Hand is intact, right?
Sorry.
I couldn't do anything to help you.
It's okay, forget it.
What can you do?
My fear is those grown up boys are
waiting to pounce on us in kabaddi.
How can we play against
these grown-ups?
In case we lose,
we'll be 'alti'
this entire month.
What does 'alti' mean?
Being an errand boy.
To be at their beck and call,
do all their dirty jobs like a slave.
I'll anyway lose.
I am agreeable to being an 'alti'
but they insist I should play, master.
I snitched to you, right?
Using kabaddi as an excuse
they plan to bash me up, master.
Hey, Undiyal!
Come.
Look here.
Look at me.
I am talking to you!
You're coming
or shall I carry you here?
More than the aches
from blows and kicks,
pain of fear hurts deeper!
Go with courage.
Go and check what he's doing.
Das, he is coming.
Tell me, Madhi.
You snitched about us
to the master, right?
- Face us now.
- Hey!
I know very well.
If Bala plays, we will win for sure.
So you got scared
and broke his hand.
Had he been here
would he have defeated us?
Of course. You would
have lost pathetically.
Call whomever, how many ever boys
you want from here to play on your side.
I'll call anyone I want, but then
you can't go back on your word.
Go ahead. We won't send you back
without breaking all your teeth today!
Master!
Clash of wills here
One foot in the grave, no fear
You are ready for your bier
Kabaddi... kabaddi... do hold your breath
Kabaddi... kabaddi... to show your strength
- Tell me, Madhi.-I checked the results.
I am sure all six of them
are above 20 years of age.
Kabaddi... kabaddi... play.
On your mark, get set full gear
Sandalwood paste smeared
One foot in the grave, no fear
You are ready for your bier
What are you saying?
Not one of them is below 18?
It's confirmed that none of those boys
are younger than 18.
On your mark, get set, ready
Bash them up deadly
Master, at least do you know
the name of this game?
This is not cricket or football.
You must hold your breath
and repeat 'kabaddi', you know?
Our rules are different.
You can't just touch and run.
You must toss your opponent
outside the line.
Still want to play?
Come on.
Kabaddi... kabaddi... kabaddi play
Kabaddi.
Kabaddi... kabaddi... kabaddi!
Go.
On your mark, get set, full gear
Sandalwood paste smeared here
Trying your tricks with us?
You are ready for your bier
Your downfall is marked
Bingo!
He got a solid slap.
Knock him down.
Kabaddi!
He deserves it!
- Superb, Master
- Come on.
He is hitting us real hard.
If you have the guts,
show it now.
Come. Come on.
Kabaddi... kabaddi... kabaddi.
- Come on.
- Kabaddi... kabaddi... kabaddi.
Lift him.
You dare lay a finger on us.
Now, wait and watch!
Come. Come on.
How dare you break a boy's hand!
- It hurts.
- This is tit for tat time.
Master, it really hurts.
Kabbadi... kabbadi... kabbadi
All set to knock you down
Lick your defeat with face on the ground
On your mark, get set, ready to lose
One step to defeat, time for the noose
Get set, sandalwood paste smeared
Hey, come on!
Clash of wills here
Be ready to lie on your bier
Kabaddi... kabaddi... touch the line
Watch the line.
If you dare lay a finger
on these boys one more time...
Kabaddi... kabaddi... hold your breath
Kabaddi... touch to show your strength
Master?
- What?
- Is it okay to talk frankly?
- Camera is recording everything.
- Go on, it's okay.
I'll tell you, Master.
My mother passed away
when I was born.
My neighbor raised me.
My father asked her
to sleep with him!
That's why
I threw the grinding stone on his head.
Immediately, the police put me in jail.
That's when Das trapped me.
From then on I was forced to listen
what Das says.
Das will walk in.
He will check who is addicted to drugs.
Powder, smoke, booze.
Then he will increase the dosage.
Which one of you here
has seen Bhavani?
Bhavani?
Where have I heard this name?
Somehow sounds familiar.
Master.
We have heard this name,
but none of us have seen him.
Das is the be all and end all here.
We must obey him.
If he asks us to surrender,
we should do so with our eyes closed.
Otherwise, we will be hanged.
They recently hanged two boys.
Didn't you see that, Master?
Do you all want to go home
and live with your family?
Or do you want to surrender?
- Go home, Master.
- Be with our family.
You have been here for ten days
and we haven't taken drugs
during this time.
Now we are ourselves.
Help us escape from here, Master.
If you follow what I say, you can
go home and live as you wish.
Will you do as I say?
- Yes, Master.
- We will.
Whatever you shared with me now,
will you tell the same to the magistrate?
Of course, we will, Master.
I'll arrange all the formalities
to get them out on parole.
Thanks, sir.
Let the video evidence
be with Charu till then.
It will reach the magistrate
when you say so.
Master, you shot some video
and cleverly made us confess.
You haven't shared your story.
Tell us. We want to know.
Come on, ask him guys.
Cat got your tongues or what?
- Tell us.
- Tell us, Master.
Please share your story, Master.
We are requesting you.
Please tell us.
Don't ask for trouble.
Trust my voice of experience!
Wait, they are very eager to hear.
I'll be happy to share.
Let them enjoy.
I was in college then.
I think it was my final year.
A new teacher joined our college.
Her name was Malar.
That love was just unbelievable.
All of a sudden the girl I loved
met with an accident.
She forgot her past.
She didn't even know who I was.
She even forgot my mad love for her.
Fate made me attend her wedding and
present her a bouquet with my own hands!
After tha--
Why are all of you
sniffling and crying?
Now that girl has totally
forgotten her past.
Master, isn't that teacher Sister Charu?
Hey, she's a teacher
and a colleague of mine.
That was my college time.
Down the memory lane.
Teacher Malar.
Don't you watch Malayalam movies?
If I don't understand the language,
- I won't watch.
- Okay.
Getting late.
All of you leave.
Class tomorrow morning as usual.
Okay, Master.
Bye, Master.
How much longer
will you quote a film story
if someone asks you
about your past life
and fool yourself and trick others too?
What film story?
Don't act.
What you narrated was the story
of the Malayalam film 'Premam'.
They stole my story
and made a movie out of it!
One track mind
on plagiarism, huh?
Okay, what do you want to know?
Tell me.
Why did you start drinking?
Every drunkard will have a story.
Why go into it now?
If I tell you my reason,
a handful of them
will follow my footsteps.
Is that necessary?
Isn't it wrong?
Okay, okay.
I won't tell you now
why I got into this habit.
If you like, I'll tell you
why I quit, shall I?
When we see those eyes of his
Won't love naturally bloom in us?
When we go close to him especially
Won't our mind skip like a deer joyfully?
Residing in her heart all the time
His style, his stride so sublime
Featuring in her dreams always
His charming dear face
He is Mr Handsome truly
He is our Master, one and only
His smile, not too much, not too less
His charisma beams through in excess
His heart is soft as a flower
Youthfulness is his signature
I pity our girls for sure
His smile is like a sparkler
He's good natured forever
This master with his class
Covers one and all en masse
If his fire work-glance falls on you
A failed heart will pass too
He is single, our news a fact
This is your chance to act
When we see those eyes of his
Won't love naturally bloom in us?
When we go close to him especially
Won't our mind skip like a deer joyfully?
JD is an orphan.
He grew up like a wild tree.
Only after joining this college,
he met a professor.
His friendship and care
changed JD's life altogether.
V. C. Selvam.
Unfortunately, he had a health issue.
He got admitted
in a hospital to get treated--
That really shattered JD.
After that he was unable to sleep.
That bloody alcohol took over him.
Residing in her heart all the time
His style, his stride so divine
Featuring in her dreams always
His endearing dear face
He is Mr Handsome truly
He is our Master, one and only
His smile, not too much, not too less
His charisma beams through in excess
Friendly gaze he sweeps
Calm and collected he speaks
No holds barred at all
All of them flip and fall
Magnetic personality
Quick and slick, sharp is he
Our master is always
Top in all ways
Some kind of innate power he displays
Endearing temerity always in place
If he stands solo, which miss
Won't yearn to be his Mrs?
When we see those eyes of his
won't love naturally bloom in us?
What--
Please move.
Hey!
Come on.
Tell me, Charu.
Sir, don't know who they are.
About three boys are chasing me.
Charu, where are you?
Which area?
In Triplicane, Murugan temple...
The road opposite Murugan temple.
- There she is.
- Charu?
Charu!
Follow me.
They started chasing me when I was
on my way to the magistrate's house.
I don't know what to do
or where to go.
Charu, don't be scared.
I will send our boys.
Go inside some shop there.
Enter a shop to be safe.
Thank you for calling, Parandhaman.
- I've come into a shop, sir.
- Turn on the speaker.
What do you need?
Brother, one minute please.
Listen to what I have to say.
Let this girl hide
in your shop for a while.
I'll send my men, please.
My business will get affected.
Don't involve me, clear out.
Aren't you a fiery blooded youth?
Speak boldly.
Brother, I'll take care.
- You don't worry.
- Thank you, Brother.
Come here, Dear.
- Did a girl come in here?
- No.
My dark and bold beauty
Why was he Uncle Scrooge?
He made my heart soft and cottony
Quake with desire, explode in rhapsody
Tell me the auspicious time
When wedding bells will chime?
- Master, they are teasing m--
- Sshh!
He made my heart soft and cottony
Quake with desire, explode in rhapsody
I told you no one came in here.
Brother, where are you going in?
Listen.
He already told you no one is here.
Oldie, shut up.
If you give it to me,
I'll give you a quick death.
Otherwise, I will--
- Hey, hey.
- Wait, Master.
This face looks familiar.
Sister.
Show him the screen.
Hey Undiyal!
Hey Button, my dear friend!
Undiyal, guys.
What are you doing
in this video call?
Hey, the girl you are chasing
is my sister.
- Your sister?
- Yes.
I didn't know that.
I was told to finish her off.
That's way I chased her down.
Well, what do you want from her?
- What is that?
- She has a camera.
I believe she has a camera.
Ask her to give it to us.
We'll leave.
Sister, give him what he wants.
We will think about it later.
Okay?
Just give it to him, Sister.
My eyes can't close at night
Without leaning on your chest in delight
Hey, Button.
I told you she's my sister.
I didn't hear your apology?
- Apologize to her.
- Sorry, Sister.
Hey! You boys too.
Sorry, Sister.
That's good.
Master, it's over.
Sister is safe.
You talk to her.
I'll wait there.
Charu, leave that place immediately.
Trust us even if we are teeny
For you, we get our hands dirty
We can steal a weapon in jail
Chase you, hot on your trail
Chew gum for flavor
Take the boys you favor
Who are you guys?
And what are you doing?
Look.
What is this tattoo?
I'll tell you.
When boys are sent to this home,
Mr. Das will pick up
the sharp ones and train them.
When we get released, he will tattoo
our hand with this Tamil letter 'pa'.
If we show this tattoo in the mess,
we can eat to our stomach's content.
If you are older, you'll get
plenty of booze and cigarettes too.
You can get clothes for free
from textile shops.
They will even get you
dope from pharmacies.
But the hitch is.
Every now and then, they will
make us surrender for a crime.
Not to get back into the old
bad ways, I'm staying aloof.
We have heard this name,
but none of us have seen him.
Das is the be all and end all here.
- We must obey him implicitly.
- Hey!
- Is it a newly released film or what?
- No one can defy him.
If he asks us to surrender,
we should with our eyes closed.
How did you lose track of him?
Don't know how, Bhavani
I sent only the professionals.
- Somehow, they messed it up--
- Shut up!
What do we do with this, sir?
It has a card inside which stores
whatever we shoot or click.
Break that card alone and
keep the camera at my place.
Okay.
When are they announcing the results?
Heard it's on Monday or Tuesday.
You'll anyway win unopposed.
Why should you be tense?
- I can enjoy, right?
- Yes, then what?
Sit here.
Do you know this ostrich?
A bird with a long neck like this.
Have you seen its egg?
It will be this big.
So big in size.
But only that ostrich will know
the pain of hatching such an egg!
How dare you sit next to me?
No, Bhava.
- Get lost!
- No, Bhavani.
Bhavani, boys want a booze party.
You won't drink anyway.
At least for them--
Drink to your death.
- Go ahead.
- Thanks a lot, Bhavani.
- Goodnight, Bhava.
- Goodnight.
Somehow you made me
show you this place.
I was staying away
from this place.
Let's go back, master.
Wait, I have a good reason.
We'll go soon.
Right, you haven't come here to eat.
- What happened to my chicken 'pakoda'?
- Narayana, serve him.
I thought you were inviting me
for a candle light dinner.
Last time I came here,
there was no power.
They had lit only candles.
Okay, relax.
Don't be disappointed with the place.
I heard the food here is incredible.
Get a token for the meals.
Madam, you too.
I thought we'll have some privacy.
Close your eyes and
show me your right hand.
- Why?
- Show, I'll tell you.
You shouldn't open your eyes
till I tell you to.
Open now.
That boy in the salon
had the same mark.
Show this over there.
And ask for meals token.
Why should I--
All for a good reason.
Go and show your hand.
Who the hell is he?
We don't differentiate or discriminate.
Whoever has the Tamil letter 'pa'
tattooed on their hands,
we'll give them whatever they ask for.
Bhavani's boys take care of the rest.
What is this for?
Still some balance left
in my bucket list!
Let the drums beat, no restraint
Let the party rock, no constraint
Let our army smash and slam
Our earth will quake with the wham
My hands will never miss a beat
When I beat the drum ever so neat
Even the dormant nerve will dance
Hearing my drum's resonance
Beat it!
Till the sun rises to a new day
Let the ground shake and sway
Till the game is won, job is done
Slow down but have your fun
Even the Lord of Death Yama will die
If he glares with his razor sharp eye
Hey boy!
Light the camphor for our Lord
He is possessed by our demi-god
Look high and low diligently
Every nook and corner and alley
There is no other big gun to defy
Or create a ruckus and vilify
Bhavani!
That master is churning in my mind.
Tell him to kill that master
tomorrow before daybreak.
Why wait till tomorrow morning?
We can finish him off right now.
Shut up and just do what I say!
Let the force of his punching fist
Make the drumhead rip and split
Let 'sound' listen to the thump and lo!
Announce who struck the blow
You there!
Let the force of his punching fist
Make the drumhead rip and split
Let 'sound' listen to the thump and lo!
Announce who struck the blow
Shaking his stupor, without a doubt
He is all set to rip your gut out
To hang you upside down
And skin you alive is his vow
Master!
Let the drums roll, no restraint
Let the party rock, no constraint
Let our army smash and slam
Our earth will quake with the wham
My hands will never miss a beat
When I beat the drum, it's a royal treat
Even the dormant nerve will dance
Hearing my drum's resonance
Rock and roll
Till the sun rises to a new day
Let the ground shake and sway.
Give me Dinkie Dow if you have.
I don't stock drugs.
Even the Lord of Death Yama will die
If he glares with his razor sharp eye
Hey, Boy
Light the camphor for our Lord
He is possessed by our demi-god
Got the man with the plan right here
Bringin' swag with the man right here
Forward all the videos
to the police department.
I'll bring the boys
to the Magistrate directly.
Okay.
Master.
That is Bhavani's truck.
I've heard he comes here often.
Let's go there.
Are you joking, Master?
I am not coming.
You go if you want to.
A whole night of merry-making
Day spent in sleep overtaking
This is the world we rejoice
Reveling in unforbidden joys
A whole night of merry-making
Day spent in sleep overtaking
This is the world we rejoice
Reveling in unforbidden joys
A whole night of merry-making
Day spent in sleep overtaking
This is our universe
for better or worse
If you move, I'll stab you.
Walk straight ahead.
What existed before birth
Knock the door.
Even you can't unearth
A secret code too!
What happens after we die
Even I don't know the right reply
If any hand reaches out to his weapon,
he will be a corpse.
Kneel, man.
- Kneel down.
- Switch off the song.
Switch it off!
Who is Bhavani here?
Which one of you here
has seen Bhavani?
What kind of sissy name
is Bhavani?
Was he lying on his stomach
as a baby when he was named?
Very good!
Let me make it clear once again.
If any of you does something stupid,
I'll cut your man's
Adam's apple, got it?
Try your luck flinging another bottle?
That means
you know Bhavani very well.
Will you go and repeat this
to him verbatim?
Bhavani, Bhavani.
A man walked right in
knowing it is your den, Bhavani.
Repeat.
No, you tell me.
I'll convey the same.
No, you are scared.
Listen, I might as well tell all of you.
The day you killed those two boys at
the Observation Home and hung them,
I hung my head in guilt and died.
I'm least bothered about myself hereafter.
Branding those juveniles with a tattoo
and making them do your dirty work.
I've put a full stop to it.
From now on, anyone wants to do anything
using the boys as lambs for the slaughter
has to kill me and then go ahead
but that has a slight hitch.
I will kill minimum ten of you
and only then breathe my last.
Be it Bhavani or Banumathi!
Will you go and tell him
word by word?
Come, get up.
Close the door.
Who threw that bottle at me?
Come here.
No, Bhavani.
I aimed it at him.
I thought the pen will fall down
and you will escape.
But I missed and--
Hey! Open the door!
- Open the door.
- Madcap!
- What false bravado!
Son of a scumbag!
Open it, damn you.
Where did you go?
Open now, I'll kill you.
- Hey! Open.
- Okay, sir.
How dare you lay a hand
on Bhavani when I'm here?
- Kottamuthu.
- Come now.
- Hey Kottamuthu.
- What did you think of us?
Brother is calling you.
Come here.
- What are you doing?
- He locked us in.
He was holding a knife
to my neck for an hour.
What the heck
were you doing then?
Bhavani, that wasn't a knife.
- It was a pen.
- You knew it, huh?
How will he open the door
if you yell after he has gone?
Shall we pen him a letter?
Sir, please open the door.
Don't hit me, Bhavani.
Who can draw well here?
Master, he is our best artist.
He's the madcap who doodles foul stuff
all over the toilet and the walls, Master.
Hi, Master.
I believe you came into my den.
Threatened a man with a pen and
conveyed an important message to Bhavani.
I am that Bhavani.
Greetings.
If you destroy all that I own,
textile shop, hotel, wine shop,
what the hell will I do?
I'm a criminal after all, right?
You assumed I wouldn't
go to the police.
Your assumption is 100% right.
But thinking you'll make
a fool of me was wrong.
I enquired about you.
I believe you have a big gang
of ardent fan followers.
Which one of them can I finish off?
I asked my boys their choice.
They said, "We can have a jolly time
killing them all without discrimination."
Let me give you a task.
Take a pen and paper.
List out your favorites
in alphabetical order.
Bhavani!
Don't ignore girls and kids
thinking I'll be soft on them.
Include their names too, okay?
Write and call each one of them.
And then, Master!
Sir!
Give me the phone.
Hello?
- Why did he hang up on me?
- Must have got scared.
Got very emotional I guess.
Why do emotional men
get so hyper and angry?
Pick, pick, pick up my call.
Pick up.
- Hi, Dude.
- Where are you?
I'm just leaving my office.
- You are safe?
- Yes, what's the problem?
Listen to me.
Don't step out.
What is the problem--
Come on, pick up.
- Sir?
- Where are you?
- Shut up---I hope you're safe?
- Yes, sir, what happened?
- Listen.
Check if our batch students
are safe, okay?
- Okay, sir.-Madhi, where is Srinath?
He is here, JD.
- What is it?
- Stay at home, don't go out.
Everything safe?
JD called me.
He was so hassled.
He told us not to step out.
Guys, don't step out of your house.
Most importantly avoid road travel.
In case you are out, go to any house
or shop nearby or any safe place.
JD sir called just now.
I think there's a major problem.
If you are safe,
for heaven's sake
text our entire group.
Park the bike.
Almost everyone in the group
texted they are safe.
But we couldn't reach
Bhargav and Savitha, sir.
Don't swerve too much to the right.
Careful!
Hello?
I am safe--
Vanathi, where are you?
In a mall nearby.
What happened?
- Is Prem with you?
- Yes.
He has gone to fetch
my purse from the car--
Vanathi, what is it?
What happened, Vanathi?
Vanathi, talk to me.
What is it?
Vanathi.
- Where are you?
- Theatre. Why, sir?
- Are you alright?
- What happened?
Sir!
Sri!
Hey!
Hey! Get out.
- What happened?
- Savitha, go.
Bhargav.
Bhargav!
Sir!
Bhargav is dead, sir.
Got the man with the plan right here
Bringin' swag with the--
Master.
How many wickets down?
According to the news I got,
two wickets down and two retired hurt.
If you are still stubborn enough
to hang out with that gang,
you'll lose 4 wickets daily.
I have never forgiven anyone
who has crossed my path till now.
This is my first time
and I am forgiving you.
Quit your job,
and leave this town.
Otherwise, the ones who escaped today
will die tomorrow.
And it will go on and on and on.
They will keep falling like ninepins.
Thank you and good bye.
Hey! Master, master.
The main reason I called you
was to tell you that I didn't lie
face down when I was named.
I was on my back,
it was clear as a bell!
- Hey!
- Yes.
I'll flay you.
Alright, come on then.
Take care of them just for today.
I'll be back soon.
Don't worry, you go.
I will ensure the safety of these boys.
- Let go of me, brother.
- Shut up and get in the truck.
- Brother, let go of me.
- I'm going to hit you.
Where are you taking me?
- I'm not coming, Brother.
- Das!
Hey! Come here.
Das, he's throwing a tantrum.
- Lift him.
- Don't force me, Brother.
- No, no.
- Bloody, listen to me.
Save me, Warden.
Don't do this, Das.
Help us, Warden.
- Don't take them.
- Let me go, Brother.
Move it.
Das! Where are you taking the boys?
Hello, sir,
I'm Thulukanam speaking.
Das and his boys have
locked us up in here.
He has taken the boys
who turned approvers
in a truck, sir.
We don't know what to do.
Please come soon, sir.
Yes, Vanathi.
This is not the end of the world for us.
You have done enough
for these boys.
I have informed the higher authorities.
They said they will be here soon.
He was chewing betel leaves in bliss
I punched his nose without a miss
You should have seen blood gush out
This Amaran's heart is gold, no doubt
Master, please take this.
I don't care two hoots
about the repercussion.
I'll take full blame.
Beat the hell out of them.
Hold this.
It's a lilting tune anyone can hum
Amaran is a seasoned singer awesome
He was chewing betel leaves in bliss
I punched his nose without a miss
Should have seen his nose bleed
This Amaran's heart is gold indee-
Hey, master is here.
Back again?
Stop it.
Are you going to hit us?
Go ahead.
Come here.
Think you've achieved
something great in life.
Shout all you want.
Hey.
Bhargav.
He is dead.
Bhargav created more trouble
in college than all of you put together.
He is dead now.
If a real rowdy reforms and just when
he wants to lead a good life, if he dies--
Do you know how cruel that is?
The faith people around him have
to turn over a new leaf will vanish.
Oh, my God!
Master has started preaching us.
Ignore them, Brother.
Why do you treat them
on an equal footing with you?
These mongrels won't reform
even if they die!
Who will reform?
When have we treated him with respect?
Or given him time, place
or an opportunity to reform?
Undiyal, Odacha Kadalai, Bottle Mani,
Soda Sekar, what kind of names?
Then how will they remember
their family or tender love and care?
Family and society alienate them.
If everybody has exiled him,
how will he reform?
Come here.
What?
The first crime committed by many here
is an emotional one.
Affection, betrayal, anger,
or a rush of adrenalin.
Each with a reason.
But after the first time.
You know what instigates you to commit
every crime you pile on to your account?
Intoxication!
I can bet on this.
All other crimes after your first was
committed losing control of your senses.
Didn't you booze?
Didn't you have a ball?
Oh! Yes, sir.
Open up your warped mind!
Only a drunkard can talk
of how it ruined his family.
Only because of my addiction
two boys lost their lives
I got that into my thick head.
I quit drinking.
Don't be such a drama queen, master!
Am I brewing liquor at home?
Blaming the buyer
instead of the seller!
That's exactly what I'm saying.
This intoxication is a political game.
You are not yet 18 years.
You can't watch this adult film.
A security guard stands out
to push you out, right?
Why is no one standing guard
outside a wine shop?
How do 10-15 years old get hold
of a booze bottle and cigarette?
Politics.
Bhavani is moving his pawn
and playing this kind of politics.
When the law is against child labor
that beast is forcing the same boys
into nefarious activities.
What is this?
What is it?
Like bribing you to vote and
you end up with an inked finger.
He gives you freebies
and brands you with a tattoo.
He has bathed you in basic amenities
providing free food and clothing.
Good Lord!
Enough of this atrocity.
You have packed those boys who believed
they have a good future into that truck.
Don't know if they will hang from a fan
or be run over by a vehicle.
But...
I will save them.
Every single one of them.
What did he say?
He will kill all those who like me?
Hey!
There are billions outside who like me.
Ask him to try his luck.
Brother, Bhavani has loaded the documents,
and money of his 'benamis' in his lorries.
He is planning to
cross the border tonight.
The boys are
in one of the trucks, Brother.
Bhavani.
All 40 lorries have crossed the border.
Expected anytime now.
Those boys?
Das is bringing them in the container.
Go.
Finish her off!
Vanathi. Vanathi.
Run over her.
Vanathi.
Vanathi, take the wheel.
Come... come.
Bang his car and kill them.
Stop... stop.
If those 15 boys turn approvers,
whom will they point their fingers at?
Das, of course.
They have never met you, Bhavani.
What if Das turns approver?
Your name, Bhavani.
Then kill Das.
Go.
Are you asking him
to get rid of me?
Your words came to my mind.
I can give up my life for you.
Give it up now.
I thought of you
as my own brother.
I regarded you as my elder brother.
Even I thought of you
as my younger brother.
What do you want me to do?
Where are the boys?
Where are they?
Hey! Go and check the container.
Go. Move it.
Bloody--
Let's see who wins.
You or me?
Das, listen to me.
Listen to me.
Just listen!
Hear me out.
Oral statement by all those boys
point fingers accusingly only at you.
They don't even know the name Bhavani.
Bhavani knows that too.
Give it a serious thought.
Will he kill all the boys?
Or kill the one they are pointing
fingers at, which is you?
- You deserve to die.
- In one swift blow, I'll--
That is not my intention.
Put an end to the killings.
I'm going to say it again.
Bhavani is very clever.
He won't kill the boys.
His target is you.
Listen to me once.
Only this time.
Ask him if you can bring the boys
in front of him. He will say no.
You insist on that, okay?
Then you'll know the true color
of Bhavani.
If this doesn't happen--
I am all yours to kill.
Master
They call me master
You know me master
I am master the blaster
Oooh yeah!
Master
They call me master
Welcome, Master.
This is the first time
we are meeting, right?
Loaded with emotion, huh?
My dear master.
Bhavani isn't just a name.
It's a kingdom I created for myself.
You can't create
a world record overnight.
If he was sharing his pearls of wisdom,
what about the mud between your ears?
You carried that boy on your waist?
Did you think they are kids?
They are killers of the worst kind.
I've already given you too much time.
Still I'll give you two minutes.
If you can--
Master, why did you hit me
while I was talking?
Didn't you ask for it?
Come.
Is this all the force you can muster?
Master.
- Master!
- Please get up, Master.
Job done and dusted.
Lord, pardon this sinner.
Don't!
Hey! I am fighting here for your sake.
So your hands don't grip
a knife once more.
Your mind.
Your mind should not
go back to its old way.
I am fighting your cause.
Not one of you.
Not even one of you
should raise his hand.
Step back.
Move back!
O master, come to my den
If you don't, I'll force you then
In my own hot spot
you bet I'm a big shot
How was it?
You're teaching a lesson
even while dying.
Is this your last lesson, master?
Come.
Shall we have it this way?
Show me your fist power.
- Hey, hey.
- Master.
- Take the boys to the truck.
- Okay, Master.
Hey, Das.
Bhavani. Bhavani.
Come my well-wisher
Raw banana fritter
I will tear your body to tatters
Fry and serve as golden fritters
Come my well-wisher
Raw banana fritter
I will tear your body to tatters
Fry and serve as golden fritters
Master... master... wait.
Sit down.
Master.
A problem won't be solved
by killing a person.
I asked a man this
when I was just 17.
And I'm going
to request you too.
Let me live.
I will do anything for you.
I won't harm those boys.
You are the one who made
those innocent children criminals.
One--
Only one year.
You were let into that Observation Home
and you've progressed so much in life.
If you are punished and sent to jail,
imagine what you'll do to this town.
I'll get into politics.
I'll start a party.
Will you join me?
Master.
What?
Job done!
Let me sing a short story
Pay attention, listen to me
If you want, take it or else
No need tension, leave it, baby
Life is very short, buddy
- Master.
- Who is that?
The boys are in the truck, Master.
Come here. Sit down.
Sit.
Shall I surrender instead of you?
Won't you understand till the very end?
Each person has to endure
the punishment according to his crime.
Madcap!
I feel I should do something for you.
Tell me if you have a family.
I'll take care of them till you're back.
I overheard the children
in the reformatory that you loved a girl.
A girl from an affluent family.
Already engaged to someone.
Shall I go and talk to her?
Maybe I can share my epic story!
Listen, my dear boy.
My name was not JD then.
Jack Daniels.
People called me Jack.
I used to draw well.
Good at card games.
In such a game we were lucky.
My friend and I won two tickets.
You would have seen everyone
run to catch a bus or train.
But imagine we ran and caught a ship
about to leave the dock.
Huh?
That's where I set eyes on her
for the very first time.
Her name was Rose.
What did you say her name was?
Rose.
Rose... Jack.
Listen to my love story.
After I fell head over heels
in love with her, I found out
she's already engaged.
After that, as we were sailing smoothly--
The ship hit an iceberg on the way.
How do you know that?
I'll wait outside, Master.
- Listen to my full epic love story.
- No need, it's okay, master.
Since manipulation of boys into crimes
by anti-social elements was proved
- with the aid of proper evidence
- Thank you, sir.
that specific govt. reformatory
was shut down permanently.
Out of the 63 inmates, those above 18
were sent to Central Prison.
And those below 18 were sent
to other govt. reformatories.
Your fingerprint over there.
Go inside.
What crime did you commit?
Baby face, partner.
Must be a gigolo.
Look at his face.
Like a parcel folded into four.
Juveniles of Nagercoil
in that Bhavani case.
I heard there were seven of them.
Only six are here.
Baby face is here.
Handsome face is missing.
Where is your master?
Must have been sent to Vellore jail.
It's even more convenient, partner.
We go to Vellore in ten days.
We'll finish him there.
Then we will meet your master in Vellore.
Transfer only after 10 days, huh?
- Are you here till then?
- Why?
Drag that 'beedi'
deep into your lungs.
This is the last 'beedi' you'll smoke.
Over dramatic punch line!
You're teaching me
about prisoners!
You might have seen
notorious prisoners
but guess who is coming now.
Master.
Master coming!
Move aside!
Safe and safeguarded
The second our commander steps in
It's like an atom bomb exploding
Master coming!
Move aside!
Deliberately if you make trouble
It will boomerang on you centuple
If you jeer or sneer at us
Mind you, you'll be limbless
Oh, no!
Tell topsy turvy
Yell curvy scurvy
Tear them to tatters
Scare them to scatter
Oh, no!
Tear them to tatters
Scare them to scatter
Master coming!
Move aside